http://www.airgas.com/privacy

We use cookies to improve your browsing experience and help us improve our websites. By continuing to use our website, you agree to our use of such cookies.
Agree
Learn more
Need an Account?
Register
or
Login
Sign up for Email |
Need an Account?
Register
or
Login
Find A Branch
Customer Service
SDS Search
Careers
Cart (0)
Switch Account
Dashboard
My Lists
Orders
Reports
Invoices
Logout
Safety Products
Privacy Policy
(Last updated January 2020 )
We know that you care how your personal information is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. Your access to, and use of, the Site is subject to Company's Terms and Conditions of Use. We have created this Privacy Policy to explain what information we gather from you when you visit our Site, how we may use this information, and the security approaches we use to protect your information. This Privacy Policy is incorporated and made part of Company's Terms and Conditions of Use.
By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Company in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. You are responsible for periodically visiting this Privacy Policy on our website to check for any changes.
1. What information is gathered?
We may collect and retain information from you when you register on the Site, place an order for products or services, respond to communication such as e-mail, or participate in another Site feature. The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your buying experience on the Site. Here are the types of information we gather:
Information You Give Us: When you are ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our Site without providing such information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many features of the Site.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us, including IP addresses and session identifiers. Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our Site. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
Information from Other Sources: For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.
2. How do we respond to “do not track” signals?
Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret web browser-based “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) signals other than cookies, we do not currently respond to, or provide visitors with a different Site experience based on, undefined “DNT” signals to the Site.
3. How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products or services, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the Site, or use certain other Site features in the following ways:
To personalize your Site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
To communicate with you.
To administer a promotion, survey or other Site feature.
To display advertising based on your likely interests (often called "interest-based ads"). For more information about interest-based ads and your choices, visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ .
To improve the Site and our product offerings.
4. Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not sell customer information to outside parties. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may disclose or otherwise transfer customer information in the following instances:
Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: We work closely with our affiliated businesses. In some cases, these businesses operate stores that interact with the Site and/or make offerings to you on the Site. In other cases, we provide services or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. When an affiliated business is involved in your transactions, we share customer information related to those transactions with that business.
Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to operate the Site and to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. Our agents have access to customer information needed to perform their functions.
Business Transfers: In the event that we sell our company, or otherwise transfer any assets of our company, we may provide your information to the purchaser so that you may continue the relationship or business with our successor.
Protection of Company and Others: We release customer information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
5. Correcting/updating customer information
You can correct or update your customer information by re-registering, updating your profile, or by contacting us at eservice@airgas.com or at OnLine Customer Service, Airgas, Inc., 259 North Radnor-Chester Road, Suite 100, Radnor, PA 19087.
6. Do we use "cookies"?
Yes. We use web tracking tools such as cookies and web beacons.
A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit those pages, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns when you click on various links and promotions throughout the Site to help us understand your preferences and to offer better experiences and tools on the Site.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our Site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf, except to help us conduct and improve our business, unless the information is anonymous with no associated personally identifiable information.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your Site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
7. How secure is information about me?
We follow generally accepted industry security standards to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, correctly use your customer information, and process online business transactions. However, no commercial method of information transfer over the Internet or electronic data storage is known to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage in our systems.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you are finished using the Site.
8. Privacy and third party links
This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our Site. In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our Site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).
9. Online policy only
This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Site and not to information collected offline.
10. Non-Personal Information
This Privacy Policy does not restrict our collection, use or disclosure of any aggregated information or information that does not identify, or cannot be reasonably linked to, any individual.
11. Questions and feedback
Any questions and feedback about the Site or this Privacy Policy should be directed to eservice@airgas.com or to OnLine Customer Service, Airgas, Inc., 259 North Radnor-Chester Road, Suite 100, Radnor, PA 19087.
12. Important notices to non-United States residents
It is important to note that the Site is operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any customer information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using the Site and/or providing us with your customer information, you consent to this transfer.
13. Your California privacy rights
If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California Privacy rights, visit www.airgas.com/california-privacy.
For any request or complaint relating to the California Privacy Policy, you can use the contact form available here.
14. Children’s privacy
We do not knowingly intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child may send an email message to ipc@airgas.com with “Request for Child Information Removal” on the subject line and the name and age of the child in the body of the message. We will then make reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from the database that stores information for the Site.
15. Contact Us - GDPR
For any request or complaint relating to the processing of your personal data and the exercise of your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you can use the contact form available here.
This form is made available in order to be put in contact with our services in charge of the protection of personal data under GDPR in the application of Airgas’ personal data protection policy.
Airgas
an Air Liquide company
Gas Supply
Cylinders
Liquid Cylinders
MicroBulk
Dynamic On-site Mixer
Jobsite Skid
© 2020 Airgas, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
